Guide to the Jerome Zerbe Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Papers, circa 1900s-2000s; Series III; 6.17; (10 boxes)
  - Clippings, photographs, correspondence, notes and other research materials, 1910s-2000s
    - Mrs. Ogden Reid, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Astors, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Elizabeth II, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Mrs. Harrison Williams, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Cornelius Vanderbilt, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Mountbattons, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Barbara Hutton, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Doris Duke, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Elizabeth Arden, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Charlie Munn Jr. and the Munns, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Tallulah Bankhead, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Frank Henderson, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Woodward, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - First Families, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Serge Obolensky, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Hedda Hopper, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Roosevelts, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Henry C. Cushing IV, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Gloria Vanderbilt Stokowski, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Perle Mesta, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Lewis Gouvernor Morris, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Duchess of Westminster, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Jimmy Donahue, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Mary Astor, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Louis Brooks, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Alfred Lunt, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Henry Ford Jr., 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Mary Paul, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Jack Astor, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Register of Society, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Condé Nast, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Howard Hughes, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Lord Milford-Haven, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Women in politics, undated (Box 148)
    - Igor Cassini, 1940s-1960s (Box 148)
    - International Set, 1950s (Box 148)
    - Martha Pudukota, 1940s-1960s (Box 148)
    - Lucius Beebe, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Mrs. Jerome Zerbe, circa 1910 (Box 149)
    - X-rays, undated (Box 149)
    - Clippings, 1940s-1950s (Box 149)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 149)
  - Other papers
    - Passports, 1920s-1970s (Box 150)
    - Notebooks, Solomon Atkinson Gorgas, 1903; 2 Folders (Box 150)
      Also contains correspondence and photographs.
    - Correspondence, 1940s-1970s (Box 150)
    - Mixed photographs and correspondence, 4 folders (Box 150)
      Also includes World War II ribbon, World War II pamphlets, and original box lid.
    - "Mostly du Barry; other papers", 1930s-1980s; 3 folders (Box 150)
    - "The Myrtle and The Rose" - Madame du Barry, draft, 1950s (Box 150)
    - "Have You Heard?" and notebook (Box 150)
    - Du Barry, 1970s (Box 150)
    - "Have You Heard?" and "The Smart Set", 1960s; 10 folders (Box 151)
    - Architectual drawings for Windsong, circa 1947; 2 folders (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Yale University degree - Jerome Brainard Zerbe, 1928 June 19 (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Windsong material, Zerbe's home in Essex Connecticut., 2 folders (Box 153)
      Plans, history, photographs, correspondence and legal papers.
    - Yale and other school materials, 1930s-1940s (Box 153)
    - Henry Sell expedition, 1963 (Box 153)
      Notebook of photographs.
    - Various prints and photographs, 1900s-1980s (Box 153)
    - Magazine and news clippings, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 153)
    - Birthday proclamation, Hassan the First, King of Afghanistan., 1980 (Box 153)
    - Calendar pages and photographs, 1935 (Box 153)
    - Windsong plaque, circa 1940s (Box 153)
    - Koch correspondence relating to images, 2000s (Box 153)
    - Koch correspondence, 2006-2008 (Box 153)
      To Fred Koch from Kevin C. Fitzpatrick.
    - Koch correspondence and photographs, 2008 (Box 153)
      Correspondence to Fred Koch from Sarah Acheson about research. Contains photographs.
    - Koch empty envelopes and sleeves, 1980s (Box 153)
    - Prints, circa 1900s-1950s (Box 154 (0versize))
    - Windsong, blue prints and map, circa 1950s (Box 154 (0versize))
    - Clippings, 1915-1950s (Box 154 (0versize))
    - Costa Rica portrait, 1978 (Box 154 (0versize))
    - Yale yearbooks and alumni material, 1928-1958; 6 folders (Box 155)
    - Eichelberger family record, 1901 (Box 155)
    - Manuscript collection index, 1989 (Box 155)
    - Index cards for people in albums (unfinished) (Box 156)
- Audiovisual materials, 1965; Series IV; 0.21; (1 box)
  Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - "J. Zerbe and Duncan MacDonald, WQXR", 1965 December 17; 1; 00:23:35 (Box 157, Item barcode 39002109975095)
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
- Printed books, 1900s-1990s; 1; (1 box) (Box A)